<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on PEI Developers</title>
    <link>/homepageBeta/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on PEI Developers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/homepageBeta/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What, exactly, is a hackathon? I’m nervous.</title>
      <link>/homepageBeta/post/what-exactly-is-a-hackathon-i-m-nervous/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/homepageBeta/post/what-exactly-is-a-hackathon-i-m-nervous/</guid>
      <description>If you’re nervous about coming out to our event, read on.
We understand. Maybe you’ve never been to a hackathon. In fact, what is it, exactly?
Our hackathon is a day-long hacking session, where peeps break-out into small, cross-functional teams to build something cool. Ideas include open data/civic hacking, games, or a hyper-local Island app — you name it. At the end of the day, teams present their work to the group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Hackathon</title>
      <link>/homepageBeta/post/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/homepageBeta/post/test/</guid>
      <description>Hello Devs, Designers, and App Fans,
PEI Developers, in partnership with generous sponsors, is happy to announce a hackathon on January 24!
Here is your invite with all the details.
This isn’t our first rodeo, so we know you may have questions. More to come, but for now, know that:
 This is a one-day event with a focus on fun and being nerdy. You don’t have to be a coder to contribute!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks!</title>
      <link>/homepageBeta/post/thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/homepageBeta/post/thanks/</guid>
      <description>PEI Hacks was a big success! Six teams demonstrated software after 8 hours of collaboration and coding. From all accounts, everyone had fun.
Over the next few days, we’ll describe the efforts and the day, but for now we want to thank so many people / sponsors.
You
Thanks again to everyone who came out. We had about 30 participants, some of whom traveled from Halifax and Fredericton, and all of whom came inside to play on a gorgeous Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>